Amanda Seals Show. Amanda Seals here and we are joined by comedian Tifran Gossary. We are in the
midst of Ficky Ficky for the record. You know how it goes. We get into the scenario. They give me
the song. When you feel like you have done the damn thing, what is the song you play? I'm gonna
have to go with All We Do Is Win. All We Do Is Win. No matter what. We just walk off, hands go up
and they stay there. And they stay there. I know that you come from an immigrant family.
How were they about you deciding to be a comic? Yeah, they don't know. So if anyone's listening
and telling my parents, I'm a doctor, just tell my dad, buh-buh, I'm a doctor. This is jokes, buh-buh.
Doctor, doctor, doctor. You know what it was? After schooling was done, they were a lot more
supportive of me doing whatever I wanted to do. And on top of that, I went to school not for them,
but for myself because I wanted to learn. Something that was really important in my family, especially
by my mom, impressed on me by my mom, was the fact that every single person in America,
especially minorities, should be as educated as possible. And no matter what we do, we should
be educated and then go forth. And then when I bought their house for them, that kind of
substantiated. By the way, they didn't need it, let's be honest. But I was like, here,
I just paid this off. They were like, comedy, comedy, comedy.